[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following tests would be appropriate to confirm the diagnosis of B12 deficiency in a patient whose B12 level is at the low end of the normal range?", "correct_answer": "Methylmalonic Acid level", "incorrect_answers": ["Urine Catecholamines", "Folic Acid level", "Haptaglobin level"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What physical feature does the lemur Aye-aye share with rodents, leading to its original classification in order Rodentia?", "correct_answer": "Very large incisors", "incorrect_answers": ["Inability to vomit", "All of these", "Similarities in the digestive system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city was Michael Jordans second professional team based?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Baltimore", "Washington", "Charlotte"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name of the fruit Persea Americana, which is native to the Caribbean, Mexico, South America and Central America?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Alligator pear", "Butter pear", "Avocado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Mohawk name of the Saint Lawrence River, Kaniatarowanenneh, mean?", "correct_answer": "Big waterway", "incorrect_answers": ["Female river", "Murmur of the gods", "Burning water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was fibromyalgia recognized as an illness by the American Medical Association?", "correct_answer": "in the 1980s", "incorrect_answers": ["in the 1990s", "in the 1960s", "in the 1970s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The giant four-legged dinosaurs such as Apatosauras and Diplodocus are known as Theropods.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A swallow hole is an unnatural depression in earths surface formed by the collapse of a large building.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What hip hop duo was featured in the 1990 comedy movie House Party?", "correct_answer": "Kid n Play", "incorrect_answers": ["OutKast", "Mobb Deep", "Das EFX"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Madison was the 3rd U.S. President.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What feature of the turtle species Dermochelys coriacea makes it easily distinguishable from all the other sea turtles?", "correct_answer": "It has no shell.", "incorrect_answers": ["It has a very long tail.", "Its body has very vivid colors.", "It has a horn on its head."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these animals are omnivorous except one.", "correct_answer": "Snail", "incorrect_answers": ["Fox", "Mouse", "Opossum"]}]